[
  {
    "answer": "• _",
    "question": "A"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A",
    "question": "• _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • •",
    "question": "B"
  },
  {
    "answer": "B",
    "question": "_ • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _ •",
    "question": "C"
  },
  {
    "answer": "C",
    "question": "_ • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • •",
    "question": "D"
  },
  {
    "answer": "D",
    "question": "_ • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "•",
    "question": "E"
  },
  {
    "answer": "E",
    "question": "•"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • _ •",
    "question": "F"
  },
  {
    "answer": "F",
    "question": "• • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ •",
    "question": "G"
  },
  {
    "answer": "G",
    "question": "_ _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • • •",
    "question": "H"
  },
  {
    "answer": "H",
    "question": "• • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• •",
    "question": "I"
  },
  {
    "answer": "I",
    "question": "• •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ _ _",
    "question": "J"
  },
  {
    "answer": "J",
    "question": "• _ _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _",
    "question": "K"
  },
  {
    "answer": "K",
    "question": "_ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ • •",
    "question": "L"
  },
  {
    "answer": "L",
    "question": "• _ • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _",
    "question": "M"
  },
  {
    "answer": "M",
    "question": "_ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ •",
    "question": "N"
  },
  {
    "answer": "N",
    "question": "_ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ _",
    "question": "O"
  },
  {
    "answer": "O",
    "question": "_ _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ _ •",
    "question": "P"
  },
  {
    "answer": "P",
    "question": "• _ _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ • _",
    "question": "Q"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Q",
    "question": "_ _ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _",
    "question": "R"
  },
  {
    "answer": "R",
    "question": "_ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • •",
    "question": "S"
  },
  {
    "answer": "S",
    "question": "• • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_",
    "question": "T"
  },
  {
    "answer": "T",
    "question": "_"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • _",
    "question": "U"
  },
  {
    "answer": "U",
    "question": "• • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • • _",
    "question": "V"
  },
  {
    "answer": "V",
    "question": "• • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ _",
    "question": "W"
  },
  {
    "answer": "W",
    "question": "• _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • _",
    "question": "X"
  },
  {
    "answer": "X",
    "question": "_ • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _ _",
    "question": "Y"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Y",
    "question": "_ • _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ • •",
    "question": "Z"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Z",
    "question": "_ _ • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ _ _ _",
    "question": "1"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1",
    "question": "• _ _ _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • _ _ _",
    "question": "2"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2",
    "question": "• • _ _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • • _ _",
    "question": "3"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "question": "• • • _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • • • _",
    "question": "4"
  },
  {
    "answer": "4",
    "question": "• • • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • • • •",
    "question": "5"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "question": "• • • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • • •",
    "question": "6"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "question": "_ • • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ • • •",
    "question": "7"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7",
    "question": "_ _ • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ _ • •",
    "question": "8"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "question": "_ _ _ • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ _ _ •",
    "question": "9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "9",
    "question": "_ _ _ _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ _ _ _",
    "question": "0"
  },
  {
    "answer": "0",
    "question": "_ _ _ _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ • • _ _",
    "question": "Comma"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Comma",
    "question": "_ _ • • _ _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • _ _ • •",
    "question": "Question Mark"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Question Mark",
    "question": "• • _ _ • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ _ _ • • •",
    "question": "Colon or Division Sign"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Colon or Division Sign",
    "question": "_ _ _ • • •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • • • _",
    "question": "Dash"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dash",
    "question": "_ • • • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ • • _ •",
    "question": "Quotation Mark"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Quotation Mark",
    "question": "• _ • • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _ _ •",
    "question": "Left Parenthesis"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Left Parenthesis",
    "question": "_ • _ _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • • _",
    "question": "Equal Sign ="
  },
  {
    "answer": "Equal Sign =",
    "question": "_ • • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ • _ • _",
    "question": "Full Stop (Period)"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Full Stop (Period)",
    "question": "• _ • _ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _ • _ •",
    "question": "Semicolon"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Semicolon",
    "question": "_ • _ • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • _ •",
    "question": "Slash or Fraction Bar"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Slash or Fraction Bar",
    "question": "_ • • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • • • • _",
    "question": "Apostrophe"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Apostrophe",
    "question": "_ • • • • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• • _ _ • _",
    "question": "Underline"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Underline",
    "question": "• • _ _ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "_ • _ _ • _",
    "question": "Right Parenthesis"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Right Parenthesis",
    "question": "_ • _ _ • _"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ • _ •",
    "question": "Addition Sign +"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Addition Sign +",
    "question": "• _ • _ •"
  },
  {
    "answer": "• _ _ • _ •",
    "question": "Commercial @ Sign"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Commercial @ Sign",
    "question": "• _ _ • _ •"
  }
]
